Thank you for watching.
I get nervous.
Yoo-hoo!
Good morning.
Yay! Here they come!
I'm a beginner.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's heavy!
I see you, Hii-chan.
Good morning.
You're so cute already.
Yes, so I, Hitomi Suzuki, have completed my first lesson!
Yay!
So cute!
Here is the normal version in the first half.
Here is the universal version.
Here is the HMV version.
Here is the stier version.
Is it good?
Can you?
Cute!
Yes, so today, I haven't seen the finished product yet either,
I'd like to take a look at it with the members.
I'm a little nervous.
Here we go!
Here is the final page!
This is the one I still wanted!
Thank you!
There's also a limited message on it.
I won't show it to you.
What! Cute!!!
This will be a kitsupepe.
So cute!
It's summer!
It was in the middle of winter in Japan,
but it was so hot in Pai.
Yes!
So cute!
Amazing!
It's Lynn!
No way!
Oh, my!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey, hey, hey.
Yay!
Wow.
That's great.
Oh, my God.
You want to see?
See?
It's so pretty.
Pretty, pretty, pretty.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's a bit of a surprise.
You're so mature.
Mature.
Grown-up.
An adult.Adults and
I can't watch this.
Wow.
No, let me see.
Let me see.
I can't...
I can't see.
I can't.
I can't!
I can't...
eh?
Wow.
It's okay now, yeah yeah yeah, I was sewing
hana
subtract 3
ah
re
Deko ار don
I can't see it.
Yes, it is.
You got to see it first.
Yay!
All right, I'll be waiting for your birthday.
I'll be waiting for your birthday.
Why?
I promised you a present.
I want the members to sign it, too.
Why not?
Please do.
It's not my birthday.
I'll consider it.
Thank you very much.
Hitomi's first photo book Hitomiburi.
It's on sale today.
Yay!
Thank you very much.